She has a
baby back there
and the neo Nazis
are planning to burn the town
A Turkish woman
was found dead up on the third floor
We're approaching
the meeting place where Johann will be expecting you
I'm not sure what
'll happen there
You do know how
to use that gun
right？
Hmm？
Calvin Street
Frankfurt，now？
My plans
have changed
Why the sudden
change of heart？
What about
killing Johann？
I'll deal
with him later
now do as I say
General Wolf will
be disappointed to hear this news
He personally
requested that you kill Johann
He believed you
were the man for the job
I don't care
I don't take
requests from anyone
I'm gonna kill
Johann of my own accord
Now hurry up and
get to Calvin Street
All ignition
points are ready to go
sir
awaiting your
orders to proceed
Well done
time to celebrate
our superiority with a little firepower
Now
What are we
gonna do with them？
These two are an
insult to our race
Unfortunately
these types do
exist among us
One is a thief
and the brat was
trying to save the Turks
They're both
filthy scum
Purify them
It's time to
teach them a lesson
This place is
gonna burn anyway
Leave them
for the flames
Oh，come on
little one
don't cry
Your mom is
coming back real soon
阿契
哎…
I can't believe
you're still alive
How'd you find me？
It's all
thanks to Dieter
He told me that
you lived in this building
Did you
say Dieter？
So then it's true
you're that Tenma guy
He was talking to
me about the other day
Where is Dieter？
Didn't he come by？
Uh…
no
Then where
'd he go？
Hey，have you
seen Aishé？
This baby is
Aishé's little boy
He needs her
he misses
his mom a lot
It can't be
No
it's not possible
I don't believe it
What about this
poor little child？
He's too young to
be without a mother
What am I
going to do？
What do I do？
She's the last
There mustn't be
any more victims
I need to see the
leaders of the Turkish quarter now
So what does
everyone think？
Set the
town on fire
huh？
Not likely
We hear rumours
about the right wing extremists all the time
We can't overreact every time they threaten us
What's even more suspicious to me is this Japanese guy waltzing in here
though he says
his life is in danger
What's the matter
with all of you？
Aisha is dead
don't you get it？
She was killed because she tried to warn all of us about this danger
I wonder
about that
She was a
prostitute like you
right？
You women go off
with Germans all the time and end up missing
That's nothing new
You make all us
Turks look bad
How do we really
know whose kid that is anyway？
You all know how
hard it is to make a living
You should know
better than to act like this
If you
want to live
and you've got
to listen to me
Forget it
do what you want
You can burn and
go to hell for all I care
Now wait
just one second
Are you suggesting patrol groups？
Maybe we should
do as this Japanese man says
We have
nothing to lose
Mr， Fanny's
Are you really
going to listen to some Asian we don't know？
He might be
suspicious
But there are certainly plenty of trustworthy Japanese people in the world
General Nogi
for example
General Nogi？
Who's he？
You mean you don'
t know about him？
General Nogi was
a brave Japanese man
who saved the
Turkish Navy
when they were
lost in the Pacific years ago
Go ahead and
gather all our men immediately
It looks
so delicious
Let's dig in
shall we？
No need to be
in such a hurry
ladies
Take your time
We wouldn't want
to finish eating before the entertainment
I planned it so
by the time the main course comes around
The show will be
reaching its climax
In the meantime
let's enjoy this
76 chateau le tour
I saved especially for this night
The first dish we
will indulge in is my favourite
raw flounder
with caviar
And as the
feast begins
Voilà
the first fire
What a
wonderful start
But like
I told you
that's still
just an appetizer
Where is the
main course？
Remember
what I said
don't be impatient
If you
savour your dinner
my show will be
something you'll truly enjoy
Tell me where
the main course is
If that's
an appetizer？
Then what are you
gonna burn for the main course？
We need more
fire extinguishers
We need to
spread out
the rest
of you men
come with me
It's just
as I thought
the flames
started upwind
This whole
place could go up
Three groups
save the
women and children
My goodness
what a
lovely surprise
And to what do we
owe this honour？
Why you old bat？
Don't even try it
or kiss your
boss goodbye
Put that
dangerous thing away
Why don't we
enjoy this meal together？
Unfortunately
it seems your
appetiser is fizzling out
Don't worry
that was just
the beginning
This is
your favourite
right？
Sorry about that
Don't be
so contrary
my dear
You see，after all
this is a
great celebration
In honour
of Johann
Listen to me
Johann doesn't
want any of this
Oh？
And tell me
how can you
be so certain？
I saw it
with my own eyes
I followed
his messages
I know
what he wants
Yohann doesn't
care about your plans
So
what exactly
did you see？
Yohann？
He doesn't
want any of this
don't you
understand？
You're right，okay
relax，calm down
just take it easy
Aishé is dead
because of you
I won't let
anybody else die tonight
So where's
the main course？
What part of town
are you going to set on fire？
Damn it
They started fires where the fire trucks can't get to
Take the injured
to the shelters
I'll be
right there
Tenma
Have you had any
luck finding Dieder？
Someone told me they saw a kid who looked like him near the park around noon
Dieder，my god
Hey
Shouldn't we go
after her and try and bring her back？
No
let's just continue with my dinner as planned
That girl
sure is something
I suppose it must
run in the family
The look she
had in her eyes
She was really
going to kill me
It's a good thing
she didn't realise
how close I was to giving her the actual location of the main course
Well
shall we bring
out the next dessert？
No
eat me some
underwear first
Huh？Scary girl
isn't she？
Hang on
我會去熄火
You made it
you're going
to be just fine
Everything's okay
alright？
I got no idea
who you are， lady
but thanks for
getting us out of there
How did the two
of you end up here
anyway？
Well， I…
You wanna know
what happened
lady？
This brat
almost got me killed
Forget this
I'm getting the
hell outta here
If that was the
smallest fire those skinheads set
I wouldn't be
a bit surprised
I grew up in
this neighbourhood
I know the place
like the back of my hand
If I wanted to
burn down the town
This wouldn'
t be the spot
believe you me
This town ain't
outta the woods just yet
There were three
other fires upwind that were also put out
We can't thank
you enough for your help
Right，everyone？
Yeah
if it weren
't for you
this all could've
been a whole lot worse
Our next step is
to take care of the injured
No
I won't have
any more victims
not one more
Wait
what are you
talking about？Well
the wind's gonna
change direction
It always happens
every night around this time
The wind
just stops
then it starts
blowing towards town from where the river is
The wind？
It stopped？
And now
time for the main
course to be served
You see them
running away？
Yes
allow me to
buy this round
Okay
that should
take care of it
Thanks for
patching me up
Doctor
Let me buy
you a drink
What are you
talking about？
You have to take
it easy for a while
Oh，come on
loosen up，Doctor
right？
That's right
it's thanks to you
we were able to
put out those fires
and save the
neighbourhood
I bet those neo
Nazis are scratching their heads right now
wondering what
the hell happened
No doubt they are
that'll teach 'em
never underestimate the Turks
Where are they
tending to all the other injured people？
The mosque
by the river
Hey，Doctor Tenma
take a break
and relax，Come on
why don't you
have a drink with us？
Not until everyone
's taken care of
If all of the
fires up until now were just diversions
Where do you think they're going to light the real fire？
How the hell
would I know？
Who cares about
this stupid town anyway？
Besides
there's something much more important on my mind that I gotta take care of
Wait
I need you
to tell me
and I need you
to tell me now
Where would you
start the real fire？
Get your
hands off of me
Like I
already told ya
the wind's gonna
come from the river
The abandoned factory down there would be a perfect place for a fire
If I'm
not mistaken
there should still be a bunch of chemicals in the warehouse
At long last
something I can
sink my teeth into
Yes
this is going
to be delicious
We're right
on schedule
The celebration
of the master race is about to begin
It's you
Why did you
follow me？
Because I have to
put out the fire
I made a
promise to Tenma
Tenma？
This is it
It's the warehouse
Thank goodness
looks like they
haven't found this place yet
These are all
filled with chemicals？
If all of this
were to go up
it'd be hopeless
There'd be
nothing left of the town
I'll protect this
place no matter what
I'm not gonna let
those horrible people burn it down
You okay？
I slipped
What the
heck is this？
Smells
like gasoline
It looks like…
someone's there
It's alright
I'm fine
I can walk
on my own
Let's get you to
a shelter so I can have a closer look at it
I twisted my ankle
It probably happened when I was trying to get away from the fire
Now that I
finally got this rug
who gives a damn
about this stinking town？
I bet I can
probably get 800
000 marks
for this baby
No，a million
Herkel
What happened to Dieter？
Couldn't say
he's probably…
Where is he？
Where'd he go？
What happened to him？
Last I saw
he was going to
the abandoned warehouse by the river
Why there？
The wind's gonna
blow in from the river soon
So if the chemicals in that warehouse are set on fire
it's all over
for this town
This is what I
was talking about
Tell everyone to
evacuate from the riverside shelters right away
Go
You're going
to take me there
Who is it？
Who's back there？
Freeze，don't move
Can it be true？
Are you really
Johann's sister？
Put the
lighter down now
Once I set this
trail of gasoline on fire
This warehouse is
going to go up in an instant
I'm going to shoot you in the head before that happens
I can fire quicker than you can flick that lighter
and I'm not
afraid to do it
And what
if you miss？
I haven't skipped
a day of training in six months straight
So I know I can
hit you from here
You don't
frighten me
Don't you know？
This is a celebration of the master race
This is our big
welcome for Johann
But Johann doesn'
t want any of the things you want
Yes
it's true that he
was recently seen here in Frankfort
But the only reason he came was to kill one of your leaders and all of his subordinates
He left a
message behind
you know
What message？
Listen to me
Johan is not the
person you think he is
The truth is much
more complex than that
What are you
trying to say？
It's worse
it must be
terrifying for him
He's suffering
he's in anguish
and teetering on the edge of despair
You know I'm not
so sure it's such a good idea
To be making
enemies of these guys
Which way to
the warehouse？
I didn't sign on
for all of this
I'm gonna call
it a day，see ya
Where the hell do
you think you're going？
Are you just
going to let Dino die like that？
Tell me where
the warehouse is
Alright
I'll tell you
just let me go
you're choking me
You told me
about your friend
You said that
his name is Tenma
right？
Would you believe
that I know a man whose name is Tenma also？
For real？
Is your Tenma
really brave too？
Yes
but he must
never fire a gun
not if I can
do it for him
I don't want
him to kill anyone
he's a good man
Killing people
is always wrong
you understand？
Even if they'
re the bad guys？
Right
Don't ever do
what I'm about to do
Close your eyes
don't look
Don't shoot
Tenma
Quick，Hekko
put out the fire
Use the rock，hurry
No
Not the rock
not the rock
1 million marks
gone
Nina
Tenma
Damn it， all the
cops are coming
Get out， go
I'll take care
of things here
There's a boat
over by the river
Please， Tenma
you have
to leave now
Hmm
My main course
it got cold
Thank you for all
your cooperation
young lady
We'd appreciate
it if you'd come down to the station
Wait one second
okay
I'll be right back
Hey，hold on
車馬
Nina
You have to
promise me something
Nina
Swear to me you
won't kill anyone
I saw it
I saw your
aunt's message
I saw it too
I'm heading there now
Ten years ago
the night I
shot my brother
I finally know
what he meant
When he told me
to shoot him in the head
Now I understand
Yohani，他…
他唔係一個人，有兩個喺入面
That's why…
Dr， Tenma
It wasn't
your fault
You didn't do
anything wrong
我必須做呢件事，我沒有其他選擇
我必須再射中約翰
Hey，wait up
What the hell are
we doing here anyway？
Come on
let's get out of here
Gotta give up
There's no use
with this guy
I guess I'll be
starving and broke forever
If only I
still had that rug
Damn it
The hell's that
supposed to be？
It's…
a message
Help
The monster
inside me…
is about
to explode
What is this
supposed to mean？
He has a
split personality？